<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <gameList>
        <game>
          <path>./bankpanic.rom</path>
          <name>Bank Panic</name>
          <desc>This must be the most dangerous job in the west! You've recently been recruited as the town's newest sheriff, but that shiny new badge of yours does nothing to scare away the crooks! The local bank is often the target of surprise bank robberies, and you've decided to take the bull by the horns and stand guard as the bank's self-appointed security officer, to shoot the robbers as soon as they show their ugly faces. But be careful! Shoot a regular customer, get shot by a robber, or allow bombs to go off and you'll be out of a job faster than you can say "skedaddle"!</desc>
          <image>./bankpanic.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20110101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1-2</players>
          <genre>Bank Panic</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./bankruptcybuilder.rom</path>
          <name>Bankruptcy Builder</name>
          <desc>This is a construction company simulation game. You assign four construction teams with different skills to construction sites, always trying to get construction projects completed in time to be able to pay the wages. The game has a simultaneous two-player mode</desc>
          <image>./bankruptcybuilder.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20080902T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Philip Klaus Krause</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1-2</players>
          <genre>Bankruptcy Builder</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./blackonyx.rom</path>
          <name>Black Onyx</name>
          <desc>Only the best of adventurers can hope to find the Black Onyx! For generations, warriors and adventurers have been drawn to the town of Utsuro to challenge the dangers of its underground tunnels, in hopes of finding the legendary Black Onyx, a stone said to give eternal youth and great wealth to its owner. Your small party of adventurers has just arrived in this town of many mysteries, and already you can smell the danger lurking at every turn. Buy equipment and hone your fighting skills, as you will need them to survive and gain experience during your quest. Prepare to engage battle with many monsters, each one more blood-thirsty than the last. Can you beat the odds and find the fabled magical stone?</desc>
          <image>./blackonyx.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20130101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Black Onyx</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./bombjack.rom</path>
          <name>BombJack</name>
          <desc>Take to the skies as you play the part of the intrepid hero Bomb Jack, the man without fear, as he indulges his incurable hobby of bomb collecting. Bomb Jack will take you around the world from Egypt to Greece, sunsoaked beaches to the skies of New York City, but don't expect a holiday in this game. Danger threatens from every side in the form of deadly robots, rogue satellites and even killer-sparrows!</desc>
          <image>./bombjack.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150330T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Bombjack RC2.2</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./boxxle.rom</path>
          <name>Boxxle</name>
          <desc>Manual labour has never been this much fun! Winning the heart of the girl of your dreams is no piece of cake, especially considering the girl in question has expensive tastes! Earn money by pushing crates inside bizarre warehouses into their intended positions. You can only push crates, not pull them, so be careful not to push a crate into a position where it can no longer be moved!</desc>
          <image>./boxxle.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Boxxle</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./buckrogerssupergame.rom</path>
          <name>Buck Rogers Super Game</name>
          <desc>The Buck Rogers space ship is in your hands! Step into the command seat of the Buck Rogers fighter for a true space adventure! Follow Buck's journey as you set out for the Planet of Zoom. An alien intelligence has taken control of the area. You must get there before the alien force devastates the planet. Buck's problems are now your problems: Fleets of alien spacecraft keep you from getting to the planet quickly and safely!</desc>
          <image>./buckrogerssupergame.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20130101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Buck Rogers Super Game</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./cavernsoftitan.rom</path>
          <name>Caverns of Titan</name>
          <desc>In the year 2045, The European Space Agency launched the second of two spaceships to Saturn's largest moon, Titan. The first mission was scrubbed after all contact was lost with the spaceship launched five years before. Upon arriving on Titan, the crew of the second mission found the wreckage of the lost spaceship, which had apparently been damaged by an unexpected dense rock belt upon entry into Titan's atmosphere. Important supply components were scattered all over the moon, and it's now the job of Astro Willy to gather these components which are vital to the mission. Guide Astro Willy through the perilous caverns of Titan, as he recovers the scattered components. But be quick about it! Astro Willy's oxygen reserves are very limited!</desc>
          <image>./cavernsoftitan.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Caverns of Titan</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./circuscharlie.rom</path>
          <name>Circus Charlie</name>
          <desc>Arcade platform game in which the player controls a clown named Charlie. Guide Charlie and help him reach the end of each stage, and rack up points along the way! One wrong move and it's bye bye Charlie! Mess up too many times and Charlie will get fired!</desc>
          <image>./circuscharlie.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20020101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Circus Charlie</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./coldblood.rom</path>
          <name>Cold Blood</name>
          <desc>You are PacSnake, a first-rank member of the glorious PacHound group, and you've been assigned to an important mission. Your orders are to break into the Ghost Heaven fortress, a high security area full of evil ghosts. Once inside, you have to eat all the blips (i.e. the yellow dots) scattered across the area. Try to avoid the patrolling ghosts, as they take no prisonners! Gobble up power icons that give you special powers for a limited time. Find keycards and other items to advance in your mission. Contact your superior over the radio at any time to get clues and intel. When all areas are clear, your mission will be complete. Good luck, soldier!</desc>
          <image>./coldblood.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Cold Blood</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./coloredgravity.rom</path>
          <name>Colored Gravity</name>
          <desc>There are two spaceships, each steered by a ColecoVision controller. At the top of the screen there are two numbers. The upper one is energy left. Energy is lost when firing, changing color or being hit by a missile. Energy recharges while the spaceship isn't accelerating or decelerating. The other number is the reload. You can't fire or change color while it's nonzero. There are three colors. Objects of different color attract each other.</desc>
          <image>./coloredgravity.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20080820T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Philip Klaus Krause</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Colored Gravity</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./commandoreturns.rom</path>
          <name>Commando Returns</name>
          <desc>The player takes control of a soldier, who starts by being dropped off in a jungle by a helicopter, and has to fight his way out singlehandedly, fending off a massive assault of enemy soldiers. Soldier is armed with a sub-machine gun as well as a limited supply of hand grenades. At the end of each level, the screen stops, and the player must fight several soldiers streaming from a gate or fortress.</desc>
          <image>./commandoreturns.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20111022T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Mr. Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Commando Returns</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./cye.rom</path>
          <name>CYE</name>
          <desc>Cye is a clone of Kye, a Boulderdash-like game. It has 42 levels, 8 of them are two-player levels.</desc>
          <image>./cye.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20130101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Philip Klaus Krause</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1-2</players>
          <genre>CYE</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./dangertower.rom</path>
          <name>Danger Tower</name>
          <desc>The plan was simple: To break into the Danger Tower and steal the world's largest diamond. But after disabling the main alarm system, finding your way to the basement and grabbing the treasure, you tripped over a secondary alarm and a horde of holobots were activated. A single electrified touch of these holobots can kill you, so you have to evade them long enough for the floor timer to count down to zero and see the stairway to the next floor appear. You must survive through all 15 floors in order to reach the top of the tower and escape!</desc>
          <image>./dangertower.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Danger Tower</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./deepdungeonadventure.rom</path>
          <name>Deep Dungeon Adventure</name>
          <desc>Once upon a time, an evil wizard stole a royal amulet and used it to cast a curse on the country's royal family. To make sure the curse would never be lifted, he hid the amulet in the Deep Dungeon, an underground lair guarded by vile creatures. Years later, after discovering your ties to the monarchy, you were told that you could claim the throne if you could only retrieve the royal amulet and break the wizard's curse. Figuring that the curse will find a way to ruin your life eventually, you venture down the stairways of the Deep Dungeon and face its terrible dangers, armed only with the hope of finding the amulet and restoring the honor of your cursed family. Can you survive long enough to succeed?</desc>
          <image>./deepdungeonadventure.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Deep Dungeon Adventure</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./destructorsce.rom</path>
          <name>Destructor SCE</name>
          <desc>A gem-collecting quest that's out of this world! Your starcruiser lands in the hostile alien city of Araknid to collect precious Crystals needed desperately on Earth. Your equipment: the mighty Ram-car. Use your Ram-car to bump Krystaloids, transforming them into precious Crystals!</desc>
          <image>./destructorsce.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20100101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Destructor SCE</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./dragonslair.rom</path>
          <name>Dragon's Lair</name>
          <desc>This special adaptation brings home all the excitement of the legendary arcade game and gives you even more control over the action! Lead Dirk the Daring on his quest to rescue beautiful Princess Daphne, who's been imprisoned in a crystal ball by the evil dragon. To complete this noble mission, you'll need courage and quick reflexes! Fend off supernatural forces with your sword or use your wits to escape. Swing on a rope over fiery chasms. Fight fierce battles with the dreaded Phantom Knight and cunning rat guards. Find a way to survive and you'll take on the most deadly foe of all, the diabolical dragon himself!</desc>
          <image>./dragonslair.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Dragon's Lair</genre>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./dungeonandtrolls.rom</path>
          <name>Dungeon & Trolls</name>
          <desc>The game is quite simple. Each participant is imprisoned in a labyrinth with only one exit door. Once inside, the door is magically locked. In order to exit, you have to find the magic key hidden somewhere in the maze.</desc>
          <image>./dungeonandtrolls.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20140408T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Dungeon & Trolls</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./frontlinesce.rom</path>
          <name>Front Line S.C.E</name>
          <desc>Uses a standard controller. Test your courage in action-packed combat! You're a lonely infantryman, fighting through treacherous terrain. The enemy comes at you from all sides. Counterattack with your pistol and grenades before it's too late! The battleground changes constantly. Watch out for deadly land mines! When enemy tanks close in, leap into your own tank! Your ultimate mission: Reach and destroy the enemy's fortress.</desc>
          <image>./frontlinesce.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Front Line S.C.E</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./frostbite.rom</path>
          <name>Frostbite</name>
          <desc>Part survivor, part architect, part nuts, Frostbite Bailey eats raw fish for sustenance but really dines on danger! Help him construct igloos by jumping on floating blocks of ice! Each igloo must be completed before the weather gets too cold, but this is certainly no easy task, as Frostbite must not only contend with water currents that make the ice blocks move in different directions, he must also avoid wild animals like snow geese, king crabs, killer clams and a bear that follows him like a shadow on the shore! Stay one step ahead of all the hazards and survive to reach the highest possible score!</desc>
          <image>./frostbite.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Frostbite</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./girlsgarden.rom</path>
          <name>Girl's Garden</name>
          <desc>Help little Papri win the heart of Minto, the boy of her dreams! Love is in the air in Papri's garden, as she secretly dreams of dating Minto, the local dream boy. Luckily, Minto loves flowers, and Papri's garden is filled with them, so all she has to do is collect enough of them and give them to Minto to gain his affection.</desc>
          <image>./girlsgarden.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20100101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Girl's Garden</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./golgo13.rom</path>
          <name>Golgo 13</name>
          <desc>Only Golgo 13 can free the hostages onboard the runaway trains! As Japan's best professional hit-man, code-named Golgo 13, you've been hired by local authorities, as a last resort, to free a group of passengers held captive onboard a number of runaway trains. In this emergency situation, there's only one way you can carry out your contract: You must drive your car alongside each train, and use your M-16 rifle to break the train's windows, in order to let the hostages escape. However, not only must you contend with incoming traffic of trains and cars that block your line of fire, you must also watch out for hostile helicopters bent on stopping you dead in your tracks. This is certainly one of Golgo 13's toughest missions!</desc>          <image>./golgo13.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20110101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Golgo 13</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./gulkave.rom</path>
          <name>Gulkave</name>
          <desc>Destroy the 8 fortresses of the Gulbas empire! As the best pilot of the fleet, you have been given control of an advanced prototype star-fighter code-named Zaiigar. Your mission - and Earth's last hope - is to destroy the 8 fortresses and turn the tide of this war.</desc>
          <image>./gulkave.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20100101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Gulkave</genre>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./helifire.rom</path>
          <name>Helifire</name>
          <desc>The player controls a submarine that shoots down helicopters. You and your men managed to enter a secret base to steal two not friendly submarines. You took control of them but while escaping the enemy’s lair the alarm was raised. Now the whole hostile army is chasing you across the sea. Will you survive? 2 players can play together on the same screen!</desc>
          <image>./helifire.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20130219T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Helifire RC1.0</genre>
          <players>1-2</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./heroesarena.rom</path>
          <name>Heroes Arena</name>
          <desc>Believe it or not, one of the most important japanese game companies is planning a ColecoVision revival! They want to use one of their classic franchises, but they're not sure which one to pick. After several hours of debate, it was decided that the main characters of these franchises would square off in a Flip Shot tournament, and the winner will see his game released on Coleco cartridges. Up to 8 human players can participate in this tournament by selecting their characters and then trying to pop their opponent's capsules by hitting the free-floating ball before the timer runs out. Each character has special abilities that can affect the ball in unexpected ways!</desc>
          <image>./heroesarena.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1-8</players>
          <genre>Heroes Arena</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./io.rom</path>
          <name>IO</name>
          <desc>The main aspect of the game is to supply enough sulphur to your HQ by building a transportation network consisting of sulphur sources, depots, roads and rail. At the start of the game, you should first connect your sulphur source to the HQ. Rail connections have higher capacity than roads, but need more time to construct. One unupgraded sulphur source supplies enough sulphur for one idle worker. Busy workers need twice as much.</desc>
          <image>./io.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>PkK (Philipp)</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>IO</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./jetp4k.rom</path>
          <name>JetP4K!</name>
          <desc>It's a side-scrolling game, where you have to avoid the incoming rocks to stay alive, and gather diamonds to sustain life.</desc>
          <image>./jetp4k.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20060101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Harvey deKleine</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>JetP4K!</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./kaboom.rom</path>
          <name>Kaboom!</name>
          <desc>Our charming Mad Bomber really doesn't mean any harm. It's just that he loves nothing better than to drop his bombs and watch them explode! Only you can stop him! As he tosses his bombs, you race to douse their fuses with your buckets of water. The more bombs that splash in your buckets, the more points you score. But, the more points you score, the faster the bombs drop! Miss a bomb, and you'll learn how "Kaboom!" got its name. Here's a true test of stamina, reflexes and concentration - Activision's Kaboom! brought to your ColecoVision by N'APA'LM Software!</desc>
          <image>./kaboom.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Kaboom!</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./kingsvalley.rom</path>
          <name>King's Valley</name>
          <desc>Vick, the notorious English adventurer from Manchester, has gone to the Valley of the Pharaohs in search of the Mystery Jewels, which supposedly hold the secret of eternal life in the Kingdom of the Sun God. These jewels were locked away in secret pyramids guarded by cursed mummies. Use knives and pickaxes left behind by the ancient egyptian builders to collect the jewels and uncover passageways to the other pyramids. Will Vick fall victim to the dreaded curse of the mummy?</desc>
          <image>./kingsvalley.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>King's Valley</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./konamispingpong.rom</path>
          <name>Konami's Ping Pong</name>
          <desc>In this challenging and realistic 8-bit simulation of Ping-Pong, you will need fast reflexes and good timing. Create strategies to defeat the CPU or a friend.</desc>
          <image>./konamispingpong.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20110101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1-2</players>
          <genre>Konami's Ping Pong</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./kralizectetris.rom</path>
          <name>Kralizec Tetris</name>
          <desc>Relive all the excitement of Tetris on your ColecoVision console! Maneuver the falling tetromino pieces to form full lines of blocks which are then removed from the pit. The pieces keep coming endlessly, so you must avoid making mistakes that may cause a random stack of pieces to form. Such a stack will cause the end of the game if it reaches the top of the pit! As you reach each new "shock" level, the falling speed of the blocks is altered, adding to the game's difficulty. After mastering the single player mode, challenge a friend with the two-player versus game!</desc>
          <image>./kralizectetris.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Kralizec Tetris</genre>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./locknchase.rom</path>
          <name>Lock 'n' Chase</name>
          <desc>Your thief's robbing a local bank. Police are in hot pursuit! Make tracks down the vault corridors. Swipe gold coins and other treasures as you go! Keep one step ahead of the law. ! Lock doors and throw cops off your trail! Collide with a cop...he's "caught". ! Keep on the run. !</desc>
          <image>./locknchase.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20121009T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Lock 'n' Chase RC2.8.2</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./mecha8.rom</path>
          <name>Mecha-8</name>
          <desc>The Earth is under attack! Prepare Mecha-8 for battle! A hero's job is never done, and today perfectly illustrates this rule: A hostile race of aliens of unknown origins have launched a vicious surprise attack on Earth's major cities! Tricia Thunder, the best mech pilot available, has been called away from her vacation to board the Mecha-8, a highly resilient war mech armed with powerful weapons. Tricia's mission is clear: She must first repel the alien onslaught to save as many civilian lives as possible, and then locate the command center of the alien menace and destroy it. But can Tricia do this single-handedly with Mecha-8? She's fully confident that she can, and you're going to help her prove it!</desc>
          <image>./mecha8.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20130101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Mecha-8</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./moduleman.rom</path>
          <name>Module Man</name>
          <desc>Rise up to the challenge of your king! The king of your kingdom is looking for a new knight to sire, and you're next in line for the post! However, the king will only give your candidacy serious consideration if you manage to bring back the coveted royal sword from the depths of his deadly dungeon!</desc>
          <image>./moduleman.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20130101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Module Man</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./mopiranger.rom</path>
          <name>Mopiranger</name>
          <desc>Mopiranger, the hero defender of Mopiland! As the Mopiranger, ride your trusty canoe through the Razzon's water castles, and free the Moplits! Use your Stone Beamer to turn the Razzons to stone, but be careful not to block yourself into a corner of the maze! Go, Mopiranger, Go!</desc>
          <image>./mopiranger.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Mopiranger</genre>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./nibbli.rom</path>
          <name>Nibbli</name>
          <desc>Slinking through an unknown land, Nibbli finds himself in an iridescent world of constant change. Gorging and gobbling, out-of-control Nibbli devours everything in sight. Still he must complete his task. He must explore glowing new worlds where even greater challenge await. As Nibbli, Nibbler's son, you must chart your course while moving at increasingly exhilarating speeds. Beware - what looks like an easy route may be the path to your destruction.</desc>
          <image>./nibbli.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20140621T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Nibbli RC1.1</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./ninjaprincess.rom</path>
          <name>Ninja Princess</name>
          <desc>She's not just a princess! She's a ninja! Armed with knives and throwing stars, she must fight her way to the provincial palace, facing hordes of cunning ninjas along the way! Can she restore peace and order to her land?</desc>
          <image>./ninjaprincess.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20110101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Ninja Princess</genre>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./ozmawars.rom</path>
          <name>Ozma Wars</name>
          <desc>War is raging in the solar system of Ozma. Alien armies invaded the area spreading death and destruction among the Human populations living on the 4 inhabited planets of this star. You are the captain of the Star End, a space ship sent to stop the enemies. Prepare for battle as the fight is going to be harsh. ! The whole mankind is threatened if this outpost falls. ! As it will be a long mission for sure, docking ships will meet you along your journey to replenish your energy.</desc>
          <image>./ozmawars.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20110622T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Ozma wars RC1.1c</genre>
          <players>1-2</players>
       </game>
       <game>
          <path>./pang.rom</path>
          <name>Pang</name>
          <desc>The balloons are coming!! - but you're not worried - you're fearless Pang, one of the Buster Bros.! You'll need to use every inch of your arcade skills to guide the intrepid adventurer through several countries shooting balloons as you go.</desc>
          <image>./pang.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20121106T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Pang RC2.0</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./peekaboo.rom</path>
          <name>Peek-A-Boo</name>
          <desc>Come play with Elmo in his play room! Introducing the latest offering from the wizards at Dvik and Joyrex, a game designed specifically for toddlers and pre-schoolers (ages 1 to 6)! Elmo of Sesame Street is hiding in his play room, and he wants to play a game of peek-a-boo with you!</desc>
          <image>./peekaboo.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20100101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Peek-A-Boo</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./pitfall2.rom</path>
          <name>Pitfall II Arcade</name>
          <desc>Pitfall Harry's quest for treasure never ends! Pitfall Harry has undertaken his most dangerous and challenging adventure yet! Deep inside a jungle infested with wild animals, and even deeper into the underground caves below, guide Harry as he locates money bags and assorted treasure, with the ultimate goal of finding a priceless crystal orb!</desc>
          <image>./pitfall2.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20100101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Pitfall II Arcade</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./princessquest.rom</path>
          <name>Princess Quest</name>
          <desc>Your princess has been captured by an evil king! The legends says that a beautiful princess was born to give happiness to a true knight. An evil king with magical powers kidnapped the princess, taking her far away to a demonic kingdom. She was made prisoner in a castle. To reach it, a knight must travel without fear through the darkness. Only a brave knight will be able to defeat the vicious monsters guarding the princess.</desc>
          <image>./princessquest.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Princess Quest</genre>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./puzzli.rom</path>
          <name>Puzzli</name>
          <desc>Max has got a cat named Kit. This cat is very special. Indeed, he can speak… and he does too much! He spends his time asking Max for food. His favourite meal? Fresh fish of course. Max knows that the cat would eat fish, but would not wet its feet. So, he has decided to go fishing, out of friendship, to feed his hungry companion. Here you are, in the middle of the ocean on your frail craft, armed with your fishing rod and some bait fish. Will you bring enough food to satisfy your greedy Kit cat?</desc>
          <image>./puzzli.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20110403T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Puzzli RC1.4b</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./questforthegoldenchalice.rom</path>
          <name>Quest For The Golden Chalice</name>
          <desc>The townspeople - including the royal guards - have all fled the kingdom, leaving the Prince alone to fend for himself, and even worse, Mardok has stolen the Golden Chalice, the greatest treasure of Larosia! It now falls to the Prince to restore the people's confidence in his royalty, and there's only one way to do it: He must return the Golden Chalice to the Yellow Castle!</desc>
          <image>./questforthegoldenchalice.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Quest For The Golden Chalice</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./santamustsavechristmas.rom</path>
          <name>Santa Must Save Christmas</name>
          <desc>9 days before Christmas. Santa deliver gift from his factory to the warehouse. But the evil Grinch have done a bad trick. All the gifts are lost in North Pole. Now, you're mission is to get back all gift before Christmas Night! Or eventually make an high score :) :)</desc>
          <image>./santamustsavechristmas.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20110101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Santa Must Save Christmas</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./schlangecv.rom</path>
          <name>Schlange CV</name>
          <desc>There are four snakes, controlled using the Colecovision controllers (two humans can play simultanously) or artifical intelligence which try to avoid running into walls and eating stuff that keeps turning up on the field.</desc>
          <image>./schlangecv.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20060101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Philip Klaus Krause</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1-2</players>
          <genre>Schlange CV</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./searchforthestolencrownjewels.rom</path>
          <name>Search For The Stolen Crown Jewels</name>
          <desc>In this game you are a prince trying to recover the stolen crown jewels needed for his coronation.</desc>
          <image>./searchforthestolencrownjewels.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20060101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Philip Klaus Krause</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Search For The Stolen Crown Jewels</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./searchforthestolencrownjewels2.rom</path>
          <name>Search For The Stolen Crown Jewels II</name>
          <desc>This game is the sequel to "Search for the Stolen Crown Jewels". A neighbouring country invaded your kingdom during the events of the first game. Now you have to fight them in the air and on the ground, in an airplane, with airship and anti-air guns, gun towers and as a special agent infiltrating and sabotaging their installations.</desc>
          <image>./searchforthestolencrownjewels2.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20070101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Philip Klaus Krause</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Search For The Stolen Crown Jewels II</genre>
      </game>  
        <game>
          <path>./searchforthestolencrownjewels3.rom</path>
          <name>Search For The Stolen Crown Jewels III</name>
          <desc>This game is the last part of the SCJ trilogy.</desc>
          <image>./searchforthestolencrownjewels3.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20100101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Philip Klaus Krause</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Search For The Stolen Crown Jewels III</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./shmup.rom</path>
          <name>Shmup!</name>
          <desc>Once again, alien forces threaten the Earth. Now it's time for you to repel the attack and save the planet, by launching a surprise attack of your own into the alien trenches where the boss ships are stationned while they get ready for the final invasion. You control a pair of space fighters that work in tandem. Collect enough fusion capsules left behind by defeated drones and your two ships will merge into a super-fighter! Can you destroy the bulk of the enemy forces before they launch their attack?</desc>
          <image>./shmup.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Shmup!</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./shouganai.rom</path>
          <name>Shouganai</name>
          <desc>As the pilot of the lone space freighter Asa Dashi, you were taken prisoner by the Funya Chin empire and arbitrarily sentenced to face the challenge of the Shouganai, a deadly game where you must pilot of caterpillar-like vehicle around an arena and grab diamonds. Avoid the patrolling alien drones at all cost, and also avoid land mines as you maneuver your vehicle along the walls of the arena and extend its "tail" to grab the diamonds. Grab all the diamonds in an arena and you then move on to the next (more challenging) arena. Upgrade your vehicle by grabbing special icons, but be careful, as some icons cause negative effects! If you survive all 24 arenas of the Shouganai, the Funya Chin empire may give you back your freedom... Maybe...</desc>
          <image>./shouganai.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Shouganai</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./shuntingpuzzle.rom</path>
          <name>Shunting Puzzle</name>
          <desc>This is a simple shunting puzzle for the ColecoVision. It has two levels corresponding to the classic Inglenook and Timesaver shunting puzzles. Move the joystick forward / backward to move the engine.</desc>
          <image>./shuntingpuzzle.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20070101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Philip Klause Krause</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Shunting Puzzle</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./squares.rom</path>
          <name>Squares!</name>
          <desc>Squares! is a fast-paced game where you need to avoid the other squares, anticipating their movement, to last as long as possible and obtain a high score. Throughout the game, the enemy squares will continuously bounce around the outer solid playfield. Your white square is bounded by the inner dashed playfield. Use the controller to guide your square away from enemy squares. Your score increases as long as your square is in play. The gameplay will become more difficult as your score increases.</desc>
          <image>./squares.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20070101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Harvey deKleine</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Squares!</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./starforce.rom</path>
          <name>Star Force</name>
          <desc>In the year 2010 of the Dimensional Almanac, a mysterious rogue planet appeared in the darkness of the cosmos. It was named Gordess, and its war-driven inhabitants plundered the resources of every planet they encountered, and left nothing but death in their wake. As the pilot of Final Star, can you put a stop to it?</desc>
          <image>./starforce.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Star Force</genre>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./starcom.rom</path>
          <name>Starcom</name>
          <desc>The nefarious Emperor Dark is trying to take over our Solar system. The Shadow Force legions with their base ships and their fighters are threatening the Earth. You, as Colonel Paul Derringer also known as "Dash", take the control of a Starmax, a Class 1 Transport Missile Cruiser, to fly into battle to destroy the enemy fleet. You will attempt to stop them in the main asteroid belt between the orbits of Mars and Jupiter.</desc>
          <image>./starcom.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120704T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Starcom RC1.0</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
       <game>
          <path>./sdf.rom</path>
          <name>StarShip Defence Force</name>
          <desc>A new alien army has defeated the Ozma solar system. Now their ships are heading towards Earth. Alien forces are too strong. The only chance for mankind is to leave Earth and find another planet far away from the aliens. Human survivors take place into starships to seek a new home. You coordinate the actions of two gunners on a starship stayed behind to stop the enemies in a crossfire.  Make sure they don't break your energy shield and destroy your spacecraft. The future of mankind is in your hands!</desc>
          <image>./sdf.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150117T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Michel Louvet</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>StarShip Defence Force RC1.1</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./straycat.rom</path>
          <name>Stray Cat</name>
          <desc>I'm Flash, the fastest Spanish cat in the city. I've spent the day wandering around with my friends, looking for some food and having fun... but I've suddenly remembered I have a date with Iris, the cutest kitty of the downtown area!! I'm already late and I have a long way to go, so I decided to race across the city rooftops to get to Iris' penthouse faster... But the rooftops are definately not safe, with obstacles around every corner! Iris is certainly worth the risk! I'll show you why they call me Flash!!</desc>
          <image>./straycat.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Stray Cat</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./subrocsupergame.rom</path>
          <name>Subroc Super Game</name>
          <desc>Fight for supremacy of the high seas! As the pilot of the Subroc sea-to-air attack vehicle, you were hailed as a national hero after single-handidly repelling the enemy army which was trying to gain control of the commercial sea shipping lines. But this victory only served to strengthen the enemy's resolve, and now they are back with a vengeance! Luckily, you are now in command of the SubRoc Mark-II, which is fully submersible, making it a force to be reckoned with on the high seas. Destroy enemy saucers, robotic boats and incoming missiles on the surface, then dive underwater to face enemy submarines and mines. Your government is counting on you!</desc>
          <image>./subrocsupergame.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20140101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Subroc Super Game</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./sudoku.rom</path>
          <name>Sudoku</name>
          <desc>To solve a Sudoku puzzle, place a number into each cell so that each row, each column, and each small 3x3 box within the larger puzzle will contain every number from 1 to 9. The game features three levels of difficulty: Novice, Adept, and Master.</desc>
          <image>./sudoku.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20080101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Sudoku</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./superactionsoccer.rom</path>
          <name>Super Action Soccer</name>
          <desc>The world's most popular sport finally comes to America! Super Action Soccer gives you the chance to be the most accomplished star player of any team that ever was. You will be involved all the time in the most exciting moments of the game. You will score the winning goal!</desc>
          <image>./superactionsoccer.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Super Action Soccer</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./thexder.rom</path>
          <name>Thexder</name>
          <desc>The private war of a lone space soldier is about to begin! No one on Earth knows from what sector of our galaxy the deadly alien drone armies came from. Only one thing is certain: They are bent on our destruction. As the pilot of an advanced Hyper Dual Armor mech, you were part of a squadron on a mission to penetrate the enemy's central computer base and destroy it. The base was heavily fortified, and your squadron was decimated, except for you. You are now trapped, alone, inside the computer complex and must traverse 10 levels against merciless automated defense systems, in an almost hopeless effort to complete your mission. While the battle rages on outside, in the deadly vacuum of space, you are about to begin your own private battle, the outcome of which may very well turn the tide of this interplanetary war!</desc>
          <image>./thexder.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Thexder</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./trackandfield.rom</path>
          <name>Track and Field</name>
          <desc>Challenge the olympic world records! Athletes from all over the world converge in a single location to proove their worth, in the greatest sports competition of all time: The olympic games!</desc>
          <image>./trackandfield.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20100101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Track and Field</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./trafficjam.rom</path>
          <name>Traffic Jam</name>
          <desc>You're Sandy Olson, a young and beautiful traffic policewoman in charge of helping hundreds of drivers face the unavoidable traffic jam caused by summer roadworks. One of those drivers is Danny Zucku, an executive who works for a very important company. He has been your friend for some time, but now you feel you want to be something more than only his friend. So you make an extra effort to help him get to his job on time, by moving the cars and trucks around the area to clear a path for Danny's sportscar. As the days pass, the traffic jams get worse, and helping Danny becomes quite a challenging puzzle for you. If Danny cannot escape the morning traffic, he may get fired!</desc>
          <image>./trafficjam.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Traffic Jam</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./txupinazo.rom</path>
          <name>Txupinazo!</name>
          <desc>You are a young Texan cowboy called Patsie, living a peaceful life at your parent's ranch. One day, you see the San Ferm?n festival on TV. After watching the 'encierro' (the famous Navarre running of the bulls) you immediately feel you must go to Spain and live that experience on your own. So, after working long hours and saving some money, you manage to buy an airplane ticket to Spain. Everything is ready to start your journey, following Hemingway's steps: Participate in eight consecutive bull runs without getting harmed. The 'fiesta' awaits you!!</desc>
          <image>./txupinazo.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Txupinazo!</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./wonderboy.rom</path>
          <name>Wonder Boy</name>
          <desc>Oh no! Tom-Tom's girlfriend Tanya has been adbucted by Drancon, the evil lizard king! Now it's up to Tom-Tom to rescue her! Through forests and caves, Tom-Tom must run, jump and toss his trusty stone hammer at dangerous animals that stand in his way, then face a boss monster at the end of each stage. Help him catch the fruits and eggs that appear before him to restore his health, and also keep an eye out for special treasures that will give you bonus points!</desc>
          <image>./wonderboy.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Wonder Boy</genre>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./zaxxonsupergame.rom</path>
          <name>Zaxxon Super Game</name>
          <desc>Challenge the evil Zaxxon in the harsh battleground of space! Alone in your space fighter, you are approaching the asteroid bases of the mighty robotic conquerer, Zaxxon! Maneuvering around gun turrets, missiles, forcefields and various airborn robotic ships, you will soon reach Zaxxon himself. But wait! Your encounter with Zaxxon is just the beginning of your mission, which will take you through additional enemy asteroids, such as the Space Port and the Alien City, towards your true final target: The Zaxxon High Command! Get ready for the ultimate challenge, in this faithful cartridge conversion of the Coleco ADAM disk game!</desc>
          <image>./zaxxonsupergame.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Team Pixelboy</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>Zaxxon Super Game</genre>
      </game>
  </gameList>